https://www.selerant.com/terms-of-use/

Terms of Use
By using the Selerant Web sites, you agree to these Terms of Use. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, you may not use the Selerant Web sites.
Terms of Use
Welcome to our Selerant website. If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy and cookies policy govern Selerant’s relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.
The term ‘Selerant ’, ‘our’, ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website, Selerant S.r.l. whose registered office is Via Leonardo da Vinci n.19 – 20051 Cassina de’ Pecchi (Milan) Italy, V.A.T. No. 10007350159. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.
The following are terms of a legal agreement between you (“You” or “Your”) and Selerant Corporation and its affiliated companies (“We” or “Selerant”). By accessing or using the Site or the Content provided on or through the Site, you agree to follow and be bound by the following terms and conditions concerning your access to and use of the Site and the Content provided on or through the Site (“Terms of Use”) and our Privacy Policy . Selerant may revise the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. The revised Terms of Use and Privacy Policy will be effective when posted.
Terms Applicable to Specific Content and Areas of the Site
Some areas of the Site or Content provided on or through the Site may have additional rules, guidelines, license agreements, user agreements or other terms and conditions that apply to your access or use of that area of the Site or Content (including terms and conditions applicable to a corporation or other organization and its users). If there is a conflict or inconsistency between these Terms of Use and the rules, guidelines, license agreement, user agreement or other terms and conditions for a specific area of the Site or for specific Content, the latter shall have precedence with respect to your access and use of that area of the Site or Content.
Reservation of Rights
The Site and Content provided on or through the Site are the intellectual property and copyrighted works of Selerant or a third party provider. All rights, title and interest not expressly granted with respect to the Site and Content provided on or through the Site are reserved. All Content is provided on an “As Is” and “As Available” basis, and Selerant reserves the right to terminate the permissions granted to you and your use of the Content at any time.
Your Content
You agree that you will only upload, share, post, publish, transmit, or otherwise make available (“Share”) on or through the Site Content that you have the right and authority to Share and for which you have the right and authority to grant to Selerant all of the licenses and rights set forth herein. By Sharing Content, you grant Selerant a worldwide, perpetual, royalty-free, irrevocable, nonexclusive, fully sublicensable license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, translate, publish, publicly perform, publicly display, broadcast, transmit and distribute the Content for any purpose and in any form, medium, or technology now known or later developed. This includes, without limitation, the right to incorporate or implement the Content into any Selerant product or service, and to display, market, sublicense and distribute the Content as incorporated or embedded in any product or service distributed or offered by Selerant without compensation to you. You warrant that: (a) you have the right and authority to grant this license; (b) Selerant’s exercise of the rights granted pursuant to this license will not infringe or otherwise violate any third party rights; and (c) all so-called moral rights in the Content have been waived to the full extent allowed by law.
You agree that you will neither use the Site in a manner, nor Share any Content, that: (a) is false or misleading; (b) is defamatory, derogatory, degrading or harassing of another or constitutes a personal attack; (c) invades another’s privacy or includes, copies or transmits another’s confidential, sensitive or personal information; (d) promotes bigotry, racism, hatred or harm against any group or individual; (e) is obscene or not in good taste; (f) violates or infringes or promotes the violation or infringement of another’s rights, including intellectual property rights; (g) you do not have the right and authority to Share and grant the necessary rights and licenses for; (h) violates or promotes the violation of any applicable laws or regulations; (i) contains a solicitation of funds, goods or services, or promotes or advertises goods or services; or (j) contains any viruses, Trojan horses, or other components designed to limit or harm the functionality of a computer. Selerant may report you to the relevant authorities and may act under the fullest extent of applicable laws if you transmit or upload content intended or designed to cause harm.
Selerant does not want to receive confidential information from you through or in connection with the Site. Notwithstanding anything that you may note or state in connection with Sharing Content, it shall not be considered confidential information and shall be received and treated by Selerant on a non-confidential and unrestricted basis and Selerant shall not take and shall not be required to take any steps to safeguard the confidentiality of any information that you Share, other than as specified in Selerant’s Privacy Policy.
Security, Passwords and Means of Accessing the Site and Content
You agree not to access or use the Site in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair any Selerant accounts, computer systems or networks. You agree not to attempt to gain unauthorized access to any parts of the Site or any Selerant accounts, computer systems or networks. You agree not to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Site or any Selerant accounts, computer systems or networks. You agree not to use any robot, spider, scraper or other automated means to access the Site or any Selerant accounts, computer systems or networks without Selerant’s express written permission.
If any of the Services require you to open an account, you must complete the registration process by providing us with current, complete and accurate information as required by the applicable registration form. You may also be required to choose a password and a user name. Access to and use of password protected or secure areas of the Site are restricted to authorized users only. You agree not to share your password(s), account information, or access to the Site with any other person. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of password(s) and account information, and you are responsible for all activities that occur through the use of your password(s) or account(s) or as a result of your access to the Site. You agree to notify Selerant immediately of any use of your password(s) or account(s) that you did not authorize or that is not authorized by these Terms of Use.
No Unlawful or Prohibited Use
You agree not to use the Site, or Content provided on or through the Site, for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use or the rules, guidelines or terms of use posted for a specific area of the Site or Content provided on or through the Site.
Indemnity
You agree to indemnify and hold harmless Selerant, its officers, directors, employees and agents from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses or expenses, including reasonable attorneys’ fees and costs, due to or arising out of Content that you Share, your violation of these Terms of Use or any additional rules, guidelines or terms of use posted for a specific area of the Site or Content provided on or through the Site, or your violation or infringement of any third party rights, including intellectual property rights.
Termination of Use
Selerant may, in its sole discretion, at any time discontinue providing or limit access to the Site, any areas of the Site or Content provided on or through the Site. You agree that Selerant may, in its sole discretion, at any time, terminate or limit your access to, or use of, the Site or any Content. Selerant may terminate or limit your access to or use of the Site if Selerant determines, in its sole discretion, that you have infringed the copyrights of a third party. You agree that Selerant shall not be liable to you or any third-party for any termination or limitation of your access to, or use of, the Site or any Content, including Content that you may have Shared.
Third Party Web Sites, Content, Products and Services
The Site provides links to Web sites and access to Content, products and services of third parties, including users, advertisers, affiliates and sponsors of the Site. Selerant is not responsible for third party Content provided on or through the Site or for any changes or updates to such third party sites, and you bear all risks associated with the access to, and use of, such Web sites and third party Content, products and services.
Disclaimer
EXCEPT WHERE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED OTHERWISE, THE SITE, AND ALL CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE, ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. SELERANT EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT WITH RESPECT TO THE SITE AND ALL CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE. SELERANT MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT: (A) THE SITE OR CONTENT WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS; (B) THE SITE WILL BE AVAILABLE ON AN UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE BASIS; (C) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SITE OR ANY CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE; OR (D) THE QUALITY OF ANY CONTENT PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU ON OR THROUGH THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS.
ANY CONTENT ACCESSED, DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED ON OR THROUGH THE USE OF THE SITE IS USED AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. SELERANT SHALL HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OR USE OF CONTENT.
SELERANT RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES OR UPDATES TO, AND MONITOR THE USE OF, THE SITE AND CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL SELERANT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA OR DATA USE, INCURRED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT OR TORT, ARISING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO, OR USE OF, THE SITE OR ANY CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE.
Exclusions and Limitations
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE DISCLAIMER OR EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE DISCLAIMER, EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN LIABILITIES. TO THE EXTENT THAT THEY ARE HELD TO BE LEGALLY INVALID, DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN THESE TERMS OF USE, DO NOT APPLY AND ALL OTHER TERMS SHALL REMAIN IN FULL FORCE AND EFFECT.
Privacy Policy
Selerant is concerned about your privacy and has developed a policy to address privacy concerns. For more information, please see Selerant’s Privacy Policy. Any personal information collected on this Site may be accessed and stored globally and will be treated in accordance with Selerant’s Privacy Policy. You understand that Selerant collects, uses, processes, possesses, and otherwise stores your personal information and utilization data and may share such data with third party service providers for the purpose of improving or providing services subject to Selerant’s Privacy Policy.
Persons Not of Age of Majority
Persons who are not of the age of majority are not eligible to use the Site, and we ask that no information in relation to such persons be submitted to us.
Export Restrictions/Legal Compliance
You may not access, download, use or export the Site, or the Content provided on or through the Site, in violation of European Union export laws or regulations, or in violation of any other applicable laws or regulations. You agree to comply with all export laws, restrictions and regulations of E.U. and Italy or applicable agency or authority, and to not directly or indirectly provide or otherwise make available any services and products of Selerant in violation of any such restrictions, laws or regulations, including, without limitation, laws, restrictions or regulations pertaining to the development, design, manufacture or production of nuclear, chemical or biological weapons or missile technology. As applicable, you shall obtain and bear all expenses related to any necessary licenses, authorizations, and/or exemptions with respect to your own use of the services of Selerant outside the E.U. Neither the services or products of Selerant nor the underlying information or technology may be downloaded or otherwise provided or made available, either directly or indirectly, into any country subject to E.U. trade sanctions, to individuals or entities controlled by such countries, or to nationals or residents of such countries other than nationals who are lawfully admitted permanent residents of countries not subject to such sanctions. By agreeing to these Terms of Use, you agree to the foregoing and represent and warrant that you are not located in, under the control of, or a national or resident of any such country.
Waiver and Severability
The failure of Selerant to exercise or enforce any rights or provisions in these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any part or provision of these Terms of Use is found to be unenforceable, such part or provision may be modified to make the Terms of Use as modified legal and enforceable. The balance of the Terms of Use shall not be affected.
Applicable Laws
All matters relating to your access to, and use of, the Site and Content provided on or through or uploaded to the Site shall be governed by the Laws of the Italian Republic . Any legal action or proceeding relating to your access to, or use of, the Site or Content shall be instituted in the courts of Milano, Italy. You and Selerant agree to submit to the jurisdiction of, and agree that venue is proper in, these court in any such legal action or proceeding.
Copyright/Trademark
Copyright© 1995-2015 Selerant and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.
Selerant, Devex, Ecodex, Regdata are registered trademarks of Selerant and/or its affiliates. Other names appearing on the Site may be trademarks of their respective owners.
Contact Information
If you have any questions regarding these Terms of Use, please contact Selerant at legal@selerant.com
Last Revised: June 30th, 2015.
Our Customers Include
Contact Us
